somiibo.com 2019-05-10

# Privacy Policy - Somiibo

Effective date: May 1, 2018

Welcome to Somiibo (“Somiibo,” “we,” “us” or “our”). Somiibo is a marketing automation platform that allows users to easily spread awareness of social media marketing and perform social signals. By visiting our website (“the website”, “the site”) using the Somiibo application (“the software”,” “the application,” “our software” or “our application”), accessing the information, resources, services, and tools that we provide, you acknowledge, understand, and agree to accept and adhere to the following terms and conditions as stated in this policy. Our Policy applies to all visitors, users, and others who access the Service (“Users”)

Our privacy policy is designed to provide transparency into our privacy practices and principles, in a format that our users can easily navigate, read, and understand. We are dedicated to treating your personal information with care and respect. If there is anything that is not clear from this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact our Support Team.

Please note that this Privacy Policy online applies to Somiibo and its Services. When using Somiibo, you may find links to other websites, apps and services, or tools that enable you to share information with other websites, apps and services. Somiibo is not responsible for the privacy practices of these other websites, apps and services and we recommend that you review the privacy policies of each of these websites, apps or services before sharing any personal data.

We reserve the right to change the Privacy Policy from time to time without notice. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review the Privacy Policy periodically to familiarize yourself with any modifications. Your continued use of this site after such modifications will constitute acknowledgement and agreement of the modified terms and conditions.

## Information We Collect:

We collect your name, email, and IP. We use Google Analytics both on the website and in the application to enhance your Somiibo experience. We use cookies to collect, track and monitor data both on the website and in the application. We do this so that we can improve the functionality of our products and ensure the safety, integrity, and fairness of users. You can read our [cookie policy here](https://somiibo.com/cookies/)

See How Google uses data when you use our partners’ sites or apps located at [www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/) for more information.

We collect some or all of this information in the following cases:

  * You register as a member on this site.
  * You fill out our contact form.
  * You browse this site.
  * You use our app.
  * You fill out fields on your profile.

We may collect non-personally identifiable information about you in the course of your interaction with our site. This information may include technical information about the browser or type of device you’re using. This information will be used purely for the purposes of analytics and tracking the number of visitors to our site.

By voluntarily providing us with Personal Data, you are consenting to our use of it in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

## How We Use Your Information:

Your name and your email are used solely for the purpose of logging into your personal account and making you a registered member of the site and app. We may also send promotional and marketing emails to you, which you can opt out of any time. We do not share, sell, or distribute your name and email without your authorization first.

Google Analytics may track additional information such as IPs which we we use for marketing.

If you submit content through our promotion pages we may use that to help with your promotion.

We may use your email address to inform you of activity on our site or to send Somiibo promotions.

Your IP address is recorded when you perform certain actions on our site. Your IP address is never publicly visible.

In an ongoing effort to better understand and serve the users of the Somiibo Services, Somiibo often conducts research on its customer demographics, interests and behavior based on the Personal Data and other information provided to us. This research may be compiled and analyzed on an aggregate basis, and Somiibo may share this aggregate data with its affiliates, agents and business partners. This aggregate information does not identify you personally. Somiibo may also disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe our services to current and prospective business partners, and to other third parties for other lawful purposes.

## How our data is stored and kept secure

We are committed to ensuring that any information you provide to us is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable measures and procedures to safeguard and secure the information that we collect.

## Sharing of Your Information:

We will not rent or sell your information to third parties outside Somiibo without your consent. In the event of a change of control, if we sell or otherwise transfer part or the whole of Somiibo or our assets to another organization (e.g., in the course of a transaction like a merger, acquisition, bankruptcy, dissolution, liquidation), your information such as name and email address, User Content and any other information collected through the Service may be among the items sold or transferred. You will continue to own your User Content. The buyer or transferee will have to honor the commitments we have made in this Privacy Policy.

## How We Store Your Information

### Your Choices About Your Information:

Your account information and profile privacy settings can be updated or changed by contacting Somiibo directly at somiibo.info@gmail.com. You may unsubscribe from email communications from us by contacting Somiibo directly at somiibo.info@gmail.com. You may request to have your account deleted by contacting Somiibo directly at somiibo.info@gmail.com.

## Children’s Privacy:

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation’s consumer protection agency enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online. We do not specifically market to children under 13.

## Request your data to be removed or deleted

If you would like your personally identifiable information to be deleted from our database you can [request deletion here](https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSfk_HSKBYb2T533kf-a-MHoY9kvUGeXPhWfXa8SzrLppiCEoQ/viewform)

## Acceptance of this policy

Use of our site signifies your acceptance of this policy. If you do not accept the policy then please do not use this site. When registering we will further request your explicit acceptance of the privacy policy.

somiibo.info@gmail.com

## Changes to Our Privacy Policy:

somiibo.info@gmail.com
